good afternoon Good afternoon from Ukraine, the city of
добрый день Добрый день из Украины город
Khmelnitsky, where are you from
Хмельницкий Вы откуда
? We are from the city of Russia.
Мы с России города Нет я не из батюшка
mask heard
маска слышали
Yes, heard the same kind of said that he
Да слышали такой же вроде сказал что не
would not renew
будет вам продлевать
deleted previous tweets wrote that he
удалил предыдущие твиты написал что
would renew shed
будет продлевать пролил
some interesting ones
какие-то интересные
where
то вы откуда
are you from Rostov region
вот Ростовская область
No, there is a city of Donetsk in the Rostov
Нет ну там есть город Донецк Ростовской
region We are not from the Rostov region, that
области Мы не с Ростовской области а то
is, you are from the Donetsk
есть Донецкой области
region  somewhere you are sitting in some Kirov or
вы где-то сидите в каком-то Кирове или
in the Urals where you say in from Donetsk
на Урале где ты говоришь в из Донецка
No we are sitting we are sitting exactly in Donetsk How
Нет мы сидим сидим именно в Донецке Как
will you prove
вы докажет
Super so cool cool How old are you How
Вот супер так круто круто Вам сколько
old
лет
are you Well how old am I 19 she is 20 cool yes
много Ну сколько мне 19 ей 20 круто да
look Let me see when  I
смотрите Давайте вот я когда людей
meet people from Donetsk, this is how they
встречаю из Донецкой вот как они говорят
say who is there Donetsk People's Republic,
там кто там Донецкой народная республика
so I always ask, I just didn’t
так я всегда спрашивают я просто не
quite live in Donetsk, more precisely, owls  didn’t
совсем жил в Донецке точнее совсем не
live in Donetsk, but you lived there like this
жил в Донецке А Вы же там жили так
Tell us in 2014 So when the
Расскажите 2014 году Так когда там
hostilities began there, you can say
начались боевые действия можете сказать
Specifically what you are interested in when the
Конкретно что интересует когда какого
hostilities began there
числа начались там Донецке боевые
on June 22 June 22 Yes, that is, up to
действия 22 июня 22 июня да то есть до
this date it
этого числа
turns out that before this Slavyansk
получается что до того как этот Славянск
Russian terrorists entered like this.
зашли типа террористы российские так
No actions of the region were
Никаких действий области не было
understood, that is, it turns out that
понял то есть получается что
if these Russian terrorists had not entered
если бы не зашли эти российские
and the militants had not begun to
террористы так и боевики не начали
arrive
приезжать
, there would have been no war,
не было никакой бы войны не было так
but listen to
но слушайте
that from both sides there are suits
тот с двух сторон тут мастей
if you count those guilty of
если так посчитать то виновных в этой
I don’t see this war, just like Ukraine, just
войне Я не вижу также как Украина также
like Russia, they are equal to each other,
как и Россия они вдвоем друг другу
how to put it, I would say that in
как выразиться равны Я бы так сказала в
terms of politics in terms of forces,
плане политики в плане сил
there’s no fault at all, I would also
вообще нет не виноват я бы еще поняли
understand that both countries are to blame to win
там обе виноваты страны выиграть Вообще
There is no one at all, as I didn’t understand it at all
никого нет как это вообще не понял
I led to this by the fact that both countries
к этому я вела то что обе страны
are to blame and to determine one of them, in
виноваты и кого-то одного определять в
principle, this is very short Ukraine, for
принципе это очень миновата Украина на
which it invaded the territory of Ross  and
что вторглась на территорию России
for example,
например
Belgorod that Belgorod in the fourteenth
Белгород что Белгород в четырнадцатом
year, tell me what was there with
году расскажите что там с Белгородом
Belgorod for 14 years, I say, and now we, of course,
было 14 год говорю а сейчас мы конечно
to shell it, these military units,
до обстреливать его эти воинские части
infrastructure facilities in Belgorod, of
инфраструктурные объекты в Белгороде
course, now from there the troops are a pond.
конечно сейчас оттуда войска пруд
Let's go back in 14, I am very
Вот давайте Вернемся 14 год мне очень
interested because when I meet
интересно потому что когда встречаю
people from  there is Donetsk Lugansk, so it’s
людей из там Донецка Луганска так это
possible to get this information first hand, it
можно из первых уст до получить эту
turns out that until June,
информацию получается что до вот июня
even so, you had no
даже так у вас Донецке никаких не было
hostilities
боевых действий
in Donetsk region on the territory of the Donetsk region until
на территории Донецкой области до 14
April 14, there were no hostilities
апреля не было никаких боевых действий
until these Russian terrorists came
пока эти террористы российские не пришли
so here you are ours  to start because
так Вот вы наш начать из-за того что
these Russian militants came Why
пришли эти российские боевики Почему
Wait, my data there was no war What was
Подождите мои данные не было войны Что
there on the Maidan
там на Майдане вас было
Didn’t people shout there against the
А разве не кричали там люди против
Donetsk region I was on the Maidan I
Донецкой области Вот я был на Майдане не
don’t remember
помню
shouting against the Donetsk region I don’t remember
кричали против Донецкой области не помню
to shout
чтобы кричать
that Yanukovych  was always behind Donetsk No,
что а Янукович всегда был за Донецком Не
well, in short, he was for his grandmother, he didn’t
ну короче был за свои бабки ему пофиг
care, and
было и на донецку
when  he ran away as a stranger he didn’t stay in the
когда он убежал чужим не остался в
Donetsk region that Den didn’t come,
Донецкой области что не приехал Дена
also true Yes That is, if it were logical
тоже верно Да То есть если бы логично
if he had left the Donetsk region for 8
если бы он был за донецкую область за 8
years, who prevented him from coming to the DPR and
лет ушел кто ему мешал приехать в ДНР и
saying Here I am guys, I suffered for you
сказать Вот я ребята я за вас пострадал
bolt he is on you  really served for us, yes,
болт он на вас служил правда и на нас да
that is, for Yanukovych that Khmelnitsky is
то есть для Януковича что Хмельницкая
my region, it was knowing the resource base
моя область это было зная ресурсная база
that you can milk
которую можно доить
damn such Kovi girls are gone, I
блин такие Кови девчата пропала обожаю
adore these people there in the Donetsk Luhansk
вот этих людей там Донецкой Луганской
region, here are the girls Yes, it turns out they
области вот девчонки Да им получается
were one of 12
был один из 12
It's not like I'm there  a propagandist or
Это не то что я там пропагандист или
someone there says that there were
кто-то там рассказывает что не было
no hostilities before the arrival of
никаких боевых действий до прихода вот
these riflemen there, and then and here the
эти там стрелковых и тогда и вот
Girl in Donetsk itself Donetsk itself
Девчонка в самом Донецке самом Донецке
until June 23, as she says. Maybe there was
до 23 июня как она говорит Может там
most likely there before or it’s
скорее всего и раньше было или это
probably when the
наверное когда
riflemen like left  Slavyansk like
стрелковцы типа вышли из Славянска типа
Donetsk
Донецк
That is, before the
Вот то есть не было до вторжения
Russian invasion, all these militants
российских вот этих всех боевиков
did not have any hostilities in the Donetsk
не было никаких боевых действий Донецкой
region
области
Yes, there were disagreements, of course, disagreements
Да были разногласия конечно разногласия
that  m someone is for trump someone is for Biden
там кто-то за трампа кто-то за байдена
there are disagreements there is someone for
есть разногласия есть кто-то за
Putin someone for Navalny there are
Путина кто-то за Навального есть
disagreements there is someone for Yanukovych
разногласия есть кто-то там за Януковича
someone is disgusting in short there are disagreements
кто-то противен короче есть разногласия
yes but this is not a military conflict this is
есть да но это не военный Конфликт это
civil Yes  maybe the political ones
Гражданский Да может политический те
come out with their rallies, those with their own.
выходят со своими митингами те со своими
This is a normal process of a normal
Это нормальный процесс нормальной
state.
государств
No one killed anyone. But the Russian
Никто никого не убивал А вот российские
militants who came and seized
боевики которые пришли да захватили
Slavyansk in 1414 began to kill people,
Славянск 14 году начали убивать людей
throw neighboring Gorlovka into the basement,
кидать на подвал Горловку соседнюю сразу
immediately there two days after Slavyansk they
же там через два дня после Славянска
killed either 15 or  On the 16th, the
убили или 15 или 16 числа убили
deputies of the city council of the Gorlovka
депутаты городского совета горловского
guy of a
парня
local resident
местного жителя никакого то там
who had come from Lvov was killed because he
приехавшего из Львова из-за того что он
hung back the flag of Ukraine in front of the
повешал назад флаг Украины перед
city council, which these
горсоветом который эти боевики
Russian militants removed everything. That is, it turns out
российские сняли все То есть получается
that the girls Yes, from the so-called DPR, they are not
что девчонки Да из так называемой ДНР не
now forced to have this passport  clearly
сейчас вынуждены этот паспорт они четко
and they say that there were no
и говорят что никаких
hostilities on the part of
боевых действий со стороны Украины не
Ukraine. It is very good that people from the DPR are
было Это очень хорошо что люди из ДНР
over  oh with them more often Here they don’t go out into the
надо с ними чаще Вот они мало выходят в
cages much Yes, because the
клетки Да потому что
Russians mostly Peals bombed there bombed
россияне в основном Раскаты там бомбили
bombs then it’s a pity that they
бомбили бомбасы тогда вот жалко что они
turned it off now we also talked
отключили сейчас мы с ним еще поговорили
about the bombing of Donbass
про бомбили Донбасс Что такое что
a day off
всем утра всем 40 пока еще выходной
when a non-working day so that civilians do not suffer
когда нерабочий день чтобы не пострадали
Ukraine hit on
мирные жители Украина ударила по
Donetsk this city's lair of
Донецком этому городскому логово
Pushilina smashed it stood for 8 years if
пушилина разнесла его стоял 8 лет если
Ukraine Bombed for 8 years
Украина Бомбила 8 лет
should
распространяйте это видео Вы должны
show What kind of zombies
показывать Что тем за зомбированным
you have in this Russian
которые есть у вас в этой Российской
Federation, what
Федерации что вот
kind of war What kind of destruction of the people of Donbass was there was none until they
Донбасса было никакого не было пока они
came to these Russian terrorists and
пришли российские эти террористы и не
started a war, and then their military
начали войну а далее своим боевые
operations masked shelling of
действия маскировали вот тут обстрелы
civilians here And so on  Bastards and
мирных жителей И так дальше [__] и
propagandists
пропагандисты